[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The jaguars extremely powerful bite, which can pierce through a turtles shell, makes it the mammal with the strongest jaw in the animal kingdom.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular herb is added to the Mojito cocktail for a refreshing flavor?", "correct_answer": "Mint", "incorrect_answers": ["Camomile", "Basil", "Rosemary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1999 movie is this quote from: Their heads werent found severed. Their heads were not found at all.?", "correct_answer": "Sleepy Hollow", "incorrect_answers": ["House on Haunted Hill", "The Blair Witch Project", "Ravenous"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Smokey and the Bandit, in order to do what cant be done, the Bandit and Cletus had to deliver the beer within how many hours?", "correct_answer": "28", "incorrect_answers": ["48", "10", "25"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Guinea pigs are very intelligent, highly social animals that use special vocalization to communicate. What does their whistling or wheeking sound express?", "correct_answer": "Excitement", "incorrect_answers": ["Danger or pain", "Discomfort", "Warning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Over the course of the complete works of William Shakespeare, the bard uses this many different words.", "correct_answer": "29,066", "incorrect_answers": ["101,009", "3030", "15,400"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not a type of map projection?", "correct_answer": "Crusoe", "incorrect_answers": ["Robinson", "Mercator", "Interrupted"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the female names Anastasia, Anastacia, Stacy, Nastassja, Nastia?", "correct_answer": "Resurrection", "incorrect_answers": ["Martyr", "Angelic", "River"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This famous head American football coach at Florida A  M College, used to say: I like my boys to be agile, mobile, and hostile.", "correct_answer": "Jake Gaither", "incorrect_answers": ["Joe Paterno", "Knute Rockne", "Peal Bear Bryant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the correct term for the sharp protuberances growing out of the stem of the rose plant?", "correct_answer": "Prickles", "incorrect_answers": ["Spikes", "Nibs", "Thorns"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital city of the Federative Republic of Brazil?", "correct_answer": "Brasilia", "incorrect_answers": ["Sao Paulo", "Bogota", "Rio de Janeiro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital of Slovakia?", "correct_answer": "Bratislava", "incorrect_answers": ["Ljubljana", "Prague", "Zagreb"]}]